AoM Records 5289
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
AoM Records
1935-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Academy of Management (AoM)
5289
29 cubic feet
29.5 linear ft.
Articles, reports, pamphlets, correspondence, minutes, publications.
This collection consists of records and files from the Academy of Management.
5566823
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 05, 2004
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2015
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of records and files from the Academy of Management.
Included are office records, correspondence, convention files, publications files, and history files.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5289 MB: AoM Memorabilia 5289 P: AoM Photographs 5289 PUBS: AoM Publications 5593: AoM Records 5772m: Keith Davis Papers 5772m: Keith Davis Papers 5772m: Keith Davis Papers 5893m: Leonard R. Burgess "Status of Women in Academy of Management" Memoir 5904m: Paul Gordon Collection of Academy of Management Miscellany 5920 AV: AoM Audio-Visual Collection 5977 mf: AoM Additional copy of publications on Microfilm 6019: AoM Eastern Academy of Management Records 6117: AoM Additional Records 6134: AoM Publications Additional Publications 6278: David Van Fleet Collection of Academy of Management Records
Arrangement
Series I. ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
Sub-Series A. GOVERNANCE DOCUMENTS Sub-Series B. ANNUAL MEETINGS. Contains programs and correspondence. Sub-Series C. EXECUTIVE OFFICERS. Sub-Series D. ACADEMY OF MANAGEMENT HISTORIANS RECORDS. Sub-Series E. COMMITTEE RECORDS. Sub-Series F. Regional Divisions. Sub-Series G. PROFESSIONAL DIVISIONS.
Worthy, James C.; Academy of Management.; Eastern Academy of Management.
5566823
- Series SERIES I. ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
  - Sub-Series A. GOVERNANCE DOCUMENTS
    - Sub-Series 1. Constitution and By-Laws: drafts and related correspondence
      - Constitution, correspondence, 1942-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, copy, 1948-1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, amendments, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Constitution and By-Laws Revisions Committee, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, revisions, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Constitution, By-Laws, and Professional Division policy statement, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        Scope and Contents
        7/27/1987
      - Miscellaneous revisions of Constitution and By-Laws (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Sub-Series 2. Board of Governors:
      Minutes of meetings, agenda items and attachments, correspondence related to meetings. Records are grouped by meeting date unless otherwise designated. Correspondence folders contain discussions on issues occurring between meetings. The Board consists of the following elected officers: Immediate Past President, President, President-Elect/Chairperson of Divisions, Vice President, 4 Professional Division Representatives, 2 Regional Division Representatives, 1 Representative-At-Large, and the following appointed officers: Editor, Academy of Management Journal, Editor, Academy of Management Review, Editor, Academy of Management Executive, and Secretary-Treasurer.
      - Board of Governors (BOG) Meeting, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 12)
        12/29/1950
      - BOG Meeting, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 13)
        12/29/1955
      - BOG Meeting, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
        12/27/1967
      - BOG Meeting, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
        Nov. 30 Dec. 1, 1973
      - BOG Meeting, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
        May 3 4, 1974
      - BOG Meeting, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
        8/17/1974
      - BOG Meeting, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
        8/21/1974
      - BOG Meeting, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
        December 6 7, 1974
      - BOG Meeting, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
        5/3/1975
      - BOG Meetings, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
        August 9, 1975 and August 13, 1975
      - BOG Meeting, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
        11/21/1975
      - BOG Meeting, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
        5/8/1976
      - BOG Meetings, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
        August 10 11, 1976 and 8/14/1976
      - BOG Meeting, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
        11/20/1976
      - BOG Meeting, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
        April 29 30, 1977
      - BOG Meeting, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
        8/13/1977
      - BOG Meeting, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 29)
        8/17/1977
      - BOG Meeting, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
        12/2/1977
      - BOG Meeting, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 31)
        April 29 30, 1978
      - BOG Meeting, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 32)
        August 8 9, 1978
      - BOG Meeting, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 33)
        8/12/1978
      - Board of Governors (BOG) Meeting, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 34)
        11/11/1978
      - BOG Meeting, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 35)
        5/5/1979
      - BOG Meeting, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 36)
        August 7 8, 1979
      - BOG Meeting, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 37)
        8/11/1979
      - BOG Meeting, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 38)
        November 30 December 1, 1979
      - BOG Meeting, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 39)
        4/26/1980
      - BOG Meeting, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 40)
        August 9, 10, and 13, 1980
      - BOG Meeting, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 41)
        12/13/1980
      - BOG Meeting, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 42)
        4/25/1980
      - BOG Meeting, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 43)
        August 1-2, 1980
      - BOG Meeting, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 44)
        8/5/1981
      - BOG Meeting, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 45)
        December 11 13, 1981
      - BOG Meeting, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 46)
        August 14 15, 1982
      - BOG Meeting, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 47)
      - BOG Meeting, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 48)
        8/18/1982
      - BOG Meeting, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 49)
        12/11/1982
      - BOG Meeting, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 50)
        4/23/1983
      - BOG Meeting, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 51)
        August 13 14, 1983
      - BOG Meeting, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 52)
        December 9 10, 1983
      - BOG Meeting, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        May 4 6, 1984
      - BOG Meeting, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        8/11/1984
      - Board of Governors (BOG) Meeting, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        12/1/1984
      - BOG Meeting, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        4/13/1985
      - BOG Meeting, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        August 10 11, 1985
      - BOG Meeting, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        12/14/1985
      - BOG Meeting, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
        4/26/1986
      - BOG Meeting, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
        August 12 13, 1986
      - BOG Meeting, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        8/16/1986
      - BOG Meeting, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
        12/6/1986
      - BOG Meeting, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        4/4/1987
      - BOG Meeting, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
        August 8 9, 1987
      - BOG Meeting, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 17)
        8/12/1987
      - BOG Meeting, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
        December 12, 1987, preliminary agenda
      - BOG Meeting, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
        December 12, 1987, agenda
      - BOG Meeting, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        December 12, 1987, minutes
      - BOG Meeting, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        April 23, 1988, preliminary agenda
      - BOG Meeting, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 23)
        April 23, 1988, agenda
      - BOG Meeting, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
        April 23, 1988, minutes
      - BOG Meeting, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 25-27)
        8/6/1988
      - BOG Meeting, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 28-30)
        8/7/1988
      - BOG Meeting, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 31)
        August 6 7, 1988, minutes
      - BOG Meeting, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 32)
        8/10/1988
      - Board of Governors (BOG) Meeting, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
        12/3/1988
      - BOG Meeting, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
        4/22/1988
      - BOG Meeting, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
        August 12 13, 1988
      - BOG Meeting, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
        8/16/1989
      - BOG Meeting, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        December 8 9, 1989
      - BOG Meeting, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        April 27 28, 1990
      - BOG Meeting, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
        August 11 12 and 15, 1990
      - BOG Meeting, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
        August 1993 August 1994, minutes
      - Executive Committee, correspondence, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 13)
        includes discussions re: reactivating the Academy
      - BOG, correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - BOG, correspondence, 1963-1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - BOG, correspondence, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - BOG, correspondence, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - BOG, correspondence, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - BOG, correspondence, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - BOG, correspondence, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - BOG, correspondence, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - BOG, correspondence, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - BOG, correspondence, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - BOG, correspondence, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - BOG, correspondence, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Board of Governors (BOG), correspondence, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - BOG, correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - BOG, correspondence, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 28)
        January June, 1987
      - BOG, correspondence, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 29)
        re: Managerial Consultation Division, July 1987
      - BOG, correspondence, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 30)
        Jul-87
      - BOG, correspondence, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 31)
        Aug-87
      - BOG, correspondence, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 32)
        September November 1987
      - BOG, correspondence, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 33)
        Dec-87
      - BOG, correspondence, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 34)
        January April 1988
      - BOG, correspondence, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 35)
        May July 1988
      - BOG, correspondence, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 36)
        August December 1988
      - BOG, correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - BOG, correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Sub-Series 3. Manuals and handbooks: Includes manuals for executive officers and general handbooks produced for members, presenting Academy organization and policies.
      - Policy Manual (Box 3, Folder 39)
        n.d. c. mid 1970's
      - Policy Manual, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 40)
        revised 8/10/76
      - Policies and Procedures Manual, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 41-43)
        revised July, 1978
      - Policies and Procedures Manual, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 44-46)
        revised August, 1979
      - Members Handbook, early draft and cost estimates, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Academy of Management (AOM) Handbook, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
        draft copy of first edition, April 1983
      - AOM Handbook, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
        draft copy for use at April 21, 1983 Board of Governors meeting
      - AOM Handbook, 1st edition, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - AOM Handbook, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - AOM Handbook, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Sub-Series 4.Leadership Directories: Listing of the leaders for all Academy organizations, from national leaders to divisional leaders.
      - Leadership Directory, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 6a)
      - Leadership Directory, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 6b)
        Oct-90
      - Leadership Directory, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 7-9)
        Oct-91
      - Leadership Directory, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 10-12)
        September 1993 August 1994
      - Leadership Directory, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series B. ANNUAL MEETINGS. Contains programs and correspondence.
    - First Annual Meeting, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Annual Meeting, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Annual Meeting, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Annual Meeting, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Annual Meeting, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Annual Meeting, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Annual Meeting, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Annual Meeting, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Annual Meeting, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      minutes
    - Annual Meeting, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      12/27/1951
    - Annual Meeting, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      program
    - Annual Meeting, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Annual Meeting, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Annual Meeting, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Annual Meeting, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Annual Meeting, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Annual Meeting, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Annual Meeting, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Annual Meeting, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Annual Meeting, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Annual Meeting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Annual Meeting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Annual Meeting, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Annual Meeting, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Annual Meeting, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Annual Meeting, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Annual Meeting, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Annual Meeting, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Annual Meeting, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Annual Meeting, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      program, 3 copies
    - Annual Meeting, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Annual Meeting, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Annual Meeting, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Annual Meeting, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      program, 3 copies each year
    - Annual Meetings (Box 5, Folder 18)
      financial records
    - Annual Meetings (Box 5, Folder 19)
      miscellaneous
  - Sub-Series C. EXECUTIVE OFFICERS.
    Academy of Management executive officers progress through three offices: Vice President and Program Chair, President-Elect and Coordinator of Professional Divisions, and President. The only contested election is for the position of Vice-President, after which the person elected automatically becomes President-Elect and then, President. Terms begin at the annual meeting in August. The Vice President is responsible for the planning and functioning of the Annual Meeting. The President-Elect is responsible for overseeing the Professional Divisions of the Academy. Included here are the files of the following officers: Ramon J. Aldag. President, 1991-1992; Arthur G. Bedeian. Vice President and Program Chair, 1986 1987; President-Elect and Coordinator of Professional Divisions, 1987 1988; President, 1988 - 1989; Janice M. Beyer. Vice President and Program Chair, 1988 1989; President-Elect and Coordinator of Professional Divisions, 1989 1990; President, 1990 1991; Alvin Brown. President, 1957; Larry L. Cummings. Vice President and Program Chairman, 1978 1979; President-Elect and Coordinator of Professional Divisions, 1979 1980; President, 1980 1981; Past President, 1981 1982; Keith Davis. President, 1964; Ralph C. Davis. President, 1948; Franklin E. Folts. President, 1953; William F. Glueck. President-Elect and Coordinator of Professional Divisions, 1978 79; President, 1979 80; Billy E. Goetz. President, 1955; Paul J. Gordon. President, 1969 70; Don Hellriegel. Vice President and Program Chairman, 1985 86; President-Elect and Coordinator of Professional Divisions, 1986 87; President, 1987 88; Herbert G. Hicks. Associate Secretary Treasurer, 1970 - 71; Secretary Treasurer, 1971 - 72; Charles L. Jamison. Founder of the Academy of Management; Fremont E. Kast. President-Elect and Coordinator of Professional Divisions, 1975 76; President, 1976 77; Steven Kerr. Vice President and Program Chairman, 1987 88; President-Elect and Coordinator of Professional Divisions, 1988 89; President, 1989 90; Harold Koontz. President, 1963; Joseph A. Litterer. President, 1970; John F. Mee. President, 1952; John B. Miner. President, 1978; Walter B. Newsom. Secretary-Treasurer and Business Manager, 1981 89; Rosemary Pledger. Vice President and Program Chairman, 1976 77; President-Elect and Coordinator of Professional Divisions, 1977 78; President, 1978 79; Dennis F. Ray. Secretary-Treasurer and Business Manager, 1976 79; Karl D. Reyer. Founder of the Academy of Management; Max D. Richards. President, 1967; Erwin H. Schell. President, 1950; John W. Slocum, Jr. Vice President and Program Chairman, 1973 74; President-Elect and Coordinator of Professional Divisions, 1974 75; President, 1975 76; Harold F. Smiddy. President, 1962; Richard M. Steers. Vice President and Program Chairman, 1984 85; President-Elect and Coordinator of Professional Divisions, 1985 86; President, 1986 87; George R. Terry. President, 1961; Stanley C. Vance. President, 1975 76; and Max S. Wortman. Vice President and Program Chairman, 1979 80; President-Elect and Coordinator of Professional Divisions, 1980 81; President, 1981 82.
    - Aldag, R., 1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Status of Minorities Task Force
    - Bedeian, A., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      December 1986 Board of Governors (BOG) Meeting, handwritten notes, n.d.
    - Bedeian, A., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Luncheon at December 1986 BOG Meeting, plans and correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      December 1986 BOG Meeting, financial records
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      December 1987 Board Of Governors Meeting, agenda correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      August 1987 BOG Meeting, handwritten notes, n.d.
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      August 1988 BOG Meeting, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Preference forms for December 1988 and April 1989 BOG Meetings
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      December 1988 BOG Meeting, agenda correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      December 1988 BOG Meeting, agenda
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      December 1988 BOG Meeting, miscellaneous agenda items
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      August 1989 BOG Meeting, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      August 1989 BOG Meeting, miscellaneous agenda items
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      "Welcome to the BOG" Letters
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      August 1989 Business Meeting, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      December 1989 BOG Meeting, miscellaneous agenda items
    - Bedeian, A., 1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      August 1990 BOG and Business Meetings, minutes
    - Bedeian, A., 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      BOG, meeting expense reimbursement
    - Bedeian, A. (Box 6, Folder 19)
      Academy of Management (AOM) Handbook, 2nd ed., correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Annual Meeting, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      Annual Meeting, BOG arrangements
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      Annual Meeting, local arrangements correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      Memos to 1987 Division Programs Chairs re: 1987 Annual Meeting, Memo #1 Memo #9
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      Memos to 1987 Division Program Chairs re: 1987 Annual Meeting, Memo #10 Memo #20
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      Annual Meeting, Doctoral Consortia, and correspondence re: divisional participation
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      Annual Meeting, Doctoral Consortia, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      Annual Meeting, program, room assignments
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      Annual Meeting, program, printing correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      Annual Meeting, program report, handwritten
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      Annual Meeting, program statistics
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      Annual Meeting, miscellaneous correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      Annual Meeting, financial records
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      Annual Meeting, associated personal expenses
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      Annual Meeting, service contract
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      Annual Meeting, new member welcome and orientation
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      Annual Meeting, pre-convention activities
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      Annual Meeting, presidential luncheon, agenda and list of attendees
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Bedeian, A., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      Annual Meeting, misc. correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 43)
      Annual Meeting, Doctoral Consortia nominations
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 44)
      Annual Meeting, memos to 1989 Division Program Chairs
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 45)
      Annual Meeting, introduction at presidential address
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 46)
      Presidential Address, August 15, 1989, "Totems and Taboos: Undercurrents in the Management Discipline"
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 47)
      Annual Meeting, Bedeian's private reception: invitation letter, guest list, and menu
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 48)
      Annual Meeting, reception invitations
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 49)
      Thank-you notes as outgoing president
    - Bedeian, A., 1990 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Bedeian, A., 1990 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Bedeian, A., 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 52)
      summary of annual meeting expenses
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 53)
      correspondence with Karl D. Reyer
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 54)
      correspondence with William B. Wolf
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 55)
      correspondence with James C. Worthy
    - Bedeian, A., 1977-1989 (Box 6, Folder 56)
      correspondence with Chuck Wrege
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 57)
      correspondence with the Secretary-Treasurer and Business Manager
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 58)
      International Programs Committee, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 59)
      Media Relations Committee, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 60)
      Membership Committee, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 61)
      Nominating Committee, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 62)
      Placement Services
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 63)
      Placement Director-Designate Search
    - Bedeian, A., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 64)
      Professional Division Policy Review Committee, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      Professional Divisions Review Committee, correspondence
    - Bedeian, A., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 66)
      Status of Women Committee, Board of Governors (BOG) report and correspondence